[A Mission of the Heart]
[مهمة القلب]
[Episode 5]
[الحلقة 5]
Go in and take a bath.
ادخل واستحم.
There's no one inside.
لا يوجد أحد بالداخل.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
My Lord!
سيدي!
Zhao?
تشاو؟
Put... Put your clothes on.
ضع... ضع ملابسك.
My virtue
فضيلتي
has been completely ruined by Huang Yu!
لقد تم تدميره بالكامل بواسطة هوانغ يو!
Commander Li,
القائد لي،
a-actually, I didn't see clearly just now.
أ-في الواقع، لم أرى بوضوح الآن.
There's no need for you to act like this.
ليس هناك حاجة لك للتصرف بهذه الطريقة.
Yes. She didn't see clearly.
نعم، لم ترى بوضوح.
How is it unnecessary?
كيف أنه غير ضروري؟
The bodies of us men of the Li family
جثث رجالنا من عائلة لي
can only be seen by our own wives!
لا يمكن رؤيته إلا من قبل زوجاتنا!
You've seen all of me!
لقد رأيتني كليا!
How can I get a wife now?
كيف يمكنني الحصول على زوجة الآن؟
How about this?
ماذا عن هذا؟
At worst, I'll marry you!
في أسوأ الأحوال، سأتزوجك!
You'll marry him?
هل ستتزوجينه؟
Do you even have feelings for each other?
هل لديكم مشاعر تجاه بعضكم البعض؟
Feelings can be developed gradually.
يمكن أن تتطور المشاعر تدريجيا.
Besides,
بجانب،
Commander Li...
القائد لي...
is good-looking and has a nice figure.
هو حسن المظهر ولديه شكل لطيف.
And he also has a decent job.
ولديه أيضًا وظيفة لائقة.
I won't suffer any loss.
لن أعاني من أي خسارة.
Zhao.
تشاو.
What do you think
ماذا تعتقد
of Officer Huang's proposal?
من اقتراح الضابط هوانغ؟
I find this proposal... inappropriate.
أجد هذا الاقتراح... غير مناسب.
Inappropriate.
غير مناسب.
Well... you're the one rejecting me.
حسنًا... أنت من يرفضني.
This chance won't come again.
هذه الفرصة لن تأتي مرة أخرى.
Don't blame me later.
لا تلومني لاحقًا.
Well... you two must be hungry.
حسنًا... لابد أنكما جائعان.
I'll go make some food for you.
سأذهب لأعد لك بعض الطعام.
I'm going now.
سأذهب الآن.
Enough. Enough.
كفى. كفى.
Why did you have to take a bath anyway?
لماذا كان عليك الاستحمام على أي حال؟
This isn't my fault.
هذا ليس خطئي.
I didn't know I'd run into Officer Huang.
لم أكن أعلم أنني سألتقي بالضابط هوانغ.
Where will you sleep tonight, My Lord?
أين ستنام الليلة يا سيدي؟
Where else?
أين أيضا؟
On the shared bed.
على السرير المشترك.
I'm afraid tonight will be a sleepless night.
أخشى أن تكون الليلة ليلة بلا نوم.
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
This is one of my private residences.
هذا هو أحد مساكني الخاصة.
From now on...
من الآن فصاعدا...
you'll live here.
سوف تعيش هنا.
Thank you, My Lord.
شكرا لك يا سيدي.
Good morning, My Lord.
صباح الخير يا سيدي.
Commander Li.
القائد لي.
What happened to your eyes?
ماذا حدث لعينيك؟
I...
أنا...
-Yeah. What's wrong? -Nothing.
-نعم. ما الخطب؟ -لا شيء.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
You complained the dorm was unclean last night,
لقد اشتكيت من أن السكن غير نظيف الليلة الماضية،
so you made us clean all night.
لقد جعلتنا نظيفين طوال الليل.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
how is Lord Shen's case investigation going?
كيف تسير التحقيقات في قضية اللورد شين؟
Lord Shen asked us to go to them.
لقد طلب منا اللورد شين أن نذهب إليهم.
Three years ago,
منذ ثلاث سنوات،
Lin Yuan's daughter, Lin Chun'er,
ابنة لين يوان، لين تشون إير
was married posthumously to Landlord Liu's son.
تزوجت بعد وفاتها من ابن المالك ليو.
But shortly after,
ولكن بعد فترة وجيزة،
the Lin family suffered a great fire.
تعرضت عائلة لين لحريق كبير.
Lin Yuan and his mother, Madam Duan, were burned alive.
تم حرق لين يوان ووالدته السيدة دوآن أحياءً.
Only the daughter-in-law, Xue Jingshu,
فقط زوجة الابن، شيويه جينغشو،
is still missing to this day.
لا يزال مفقودًا حتى يومنا هذا.
So Lord Shen, you suspect...
إذن يا سيد شين، أنت تشك...
the murderer is Xue Jingshu?
هل Xue Jingshu هو القاتل؟
She closely matches the characteristics you described.
إنها تتطابق بشكل وثيق مع الخصائص التي وصفتها.
The ghost bride case
قضية العروس الشبح
and the Lin family case have completely different modus operandi.
وقضية عائلة لين لها أسلوب عمل مختلف تماما.
So we didn't connect them before.
لذلك لم نربطهم من قبل.
Then does Zhao Yutang
ثم يفعل تشاو يوتانغ
know about this?
هل تعلم عن هذا؟
Zhao Mansion's butler, Zhao Ming, took all the blame.
لقد تحمل كبير الخدم في قصر تشاو، تشاو مينغ، كل اللوم.
Strange.
غريب.
Without his master's approval,
بدون موافقة سيده،
would Zhao Ming dare decide on his own?
هل يجرؤ تشاو مينغ على اتخاذ قرار بمفرده؟
There's no perfect crime.
لا توجد جريمة مثالية.
The fox's tail will show sooner or later.
ذيل الثعلب سوف يظهر عاجلا أم آجلا.
The top priority now
الأولوية القصوى الآن
is to figure out how to catch this killer.
هو معرفة كيفية القبض على هذا القاتل.
That's the difficult part.
هذا هو الجزء الصعب.
Xue Jingshu is elusive and highly skilled in martial arts.
شيو جينغشو هو شخص مراوغ وذو مهارة عالية في فنون الدفاع عن النفس.
Last time we only happened to encounter her going after Madam Wang.
في المرة الأخيرة صادفنا أنها كانت تلاحق السيدة وانج.
And in the end, she still got away.
وفي النهاية، تمكنت من الهرب.
Now we really don't know where to find her.
والآن لا نعرف حقًا أين نجدها.
But I looked into her past.
ولكنني نظرت إلى ماضيها.
She's just an ordinary person.
إنها مجرد شخص عادي.
God knows where she learned such strange martial arts.
الله أعلم أين تعلمت مثل هذه الفنون القتالية الغريبة.
An ordinary person?
شخص عادي؟
Since we can't find the killer,
وبما أننا لا نستطيع العثور على القاتل،
why not try to make the killer come to us?
لماذا لا نحاول أن نجعل القاتل يأتي إلينا؟
I never thought you'd become someone working for the authorities.
لم أكن أتوقع أبدًا أنك ستصبح شخصًا يعمل لصالح السلطات.
You know me?
أنت تعرفني؟
When Chun'er was humiliated on the street,
عندما تعرضت تشون إير للإذلال في الشارع،
I was powerless.
لقد كنت عاجزا.
Fortunately, you came to our aid.
لحسن الحظ أنك أتيت لمساعدتنا.
Get lost!
اغرب عن وجهي!
It's not safe at night.
إنه ليس آمنًا في الليل.
I'll escort you home. Let's go.
سأرافقك إلى المنزل. هيا بنا.
So that's why you spared me on the night
لهذا السبب أنقذتني في تلك الليلة
of the ghost wedding at Zhao Mansion?
من حفل زفاف الشبح في قصر تشاو؟
I know you're a good person.
أعلم أنك شخص جيد.
If only this world...
لو كان هذا العالم...
had a few more people like you.
كان هناك عدد قليل من الناس مثلك.
Chun'er barely escaped that disaster,
نجا تشون إير بصعوبة من تلك الكارثة،
but what I never expected was...
ولكن ما لم أتوقعه أبدًا هو...
that beast Lin Yuan...
هذا الوحش لين يوان...
actually sold her to Landlord Liu's son for a ghost marriage.
في الواقع، باعها إلى ابن مالك العقار ليو لزواج شبح.
They destroyed Chun'er.
لقد دمروا تشون إير.
I want them to join Chun'er in death.
أريد منهم أن ينضموا إلى تشون إير في الموت.
But as far as I know,
ولكن بقدر ما أعلم،
you didn't know martial arts before.
لم تكن تعرف فنون القتال من قبل.
Where did you learn these skills?
أين تعلمت هذه المهارات؟
After Lin Yuan caused Chun'er's death,
بعد أن تسبب لين يوان في وفاة تشون إير،
he also drove me out of the family.
لقد طردني أيضًا من العائلة.
You caused my daughter's death!
لقد تسببت في موت ابنتي!
I want you to pay with your life!
أريدك أن تدفع بحياتك!
Stop talking nonsense!
توقف عن الكلام الهراء!
That lowly girl's birth characters
شخصيات ميلاد تلك الفتاة المتواضعة
matched Landlord Liu's son's!
مطابقة لابن المالك ليو!
It was her good fortune!
لقد كان حظها سعيدا!
Don't go!
لا تذهب!
Lin Yuan!
لين يوان!
I won't let you off even if it costs my life!
لن أسمح لك بالخروج حتى لو كلفني ذلك حياتي!
Do you want to avenge your daughter?
هل تريد الانتقام لابنتك؟
I can help you.
أستطيع مساعدتك.
A ghost-masked man?
رجل مقنع الشبح؟
He knew my suffering
لقد عرف معاناتي
and gave me a bowl of medicine to drink.
وأعطوني وعاءً من الدواء لأشربه.
And then I gained the skills needed for revenge.
وبعدها اكتسبت المهارات اللازمة للانتقام.
But...
لكن...
why did he help you?
لماذا ساعدك؟
He didn't tell me.
لم يخبرني.
He only told me...
لقد قال لي فقط...
to bury Chun'er properly.
لدفن تشون إير بشكل صحيح.
So,
لذا،
you're also the perpetrator of the previous ghost marriage cases?
هل أنت أيضًا مرتكب حالات زواج الأشباح السابقة؟
In order
بالترتيب
to arrange ghost marriages for their sons,
لترتيب زيجات الأشباح لأبنائهم،
they harmed other people's daughters.
لقد أذوا بنات الآخرين.
And the other one, for just a little money,
والأخرى، مقابل القليل من المال،
harmed his own daughter.
أذى ابنته.
Such beasts—
مثل هذه الوحوش-
do they deserve to live?
هل يستحقون العيش؟
Where are the women
أين النساء
you stole?
هل سرقت؟
I gave them proper burials.
لقد قمت بدفنهم بشكل لائق.
They were sold cheaply while alive.
لقد تم بيعهم بثمن بخس وهم على قيد الحياة.
After death...
بعد الموت...
they should at least have some peace.
ينبغي لهم على الأقل أن يتمتعوا ببعض السلام.
My Lord,
سيدي
tell me,
أخبرني،
why is this world so unfair
لماذا هذا العالم غير عادل؟
to women?
للنساء؟
Yu.
يو.
You contributed a lot
لقد ساهمت كثيرًا
to solving this case.
لحل هذه القضية.
I'll reward you generously tomorrow.
سأكافئك بسخاء غدا.
Thank you, My Lord.
شكرا لك يا سيدي.
I've only been working as an officer for a short time,
لقد عملت كضابط لفترة قصيرة فقط،
but I've lost so much hair.
ولكنني فقدت الكثير من شعري.
If this continues, I'll go bald!
إذا استمر هذا الأمر، سأصبح أصلع!
My life is too hard!
حياتي صعبة للغاية!
But
لكن
if I can earn this much every time, it would be nice.
إذا تمكنت من كسب هذا القدر في كل مرة، فسيكون الأمر رائعًا.
Then I wouldn't have to worry about retirement.
حينها لن أضطر للقلق بشأن التقاعد.
Lord Shen truly understands me.
اللورد شين يفهمني حقًا.
Look at your mercenary attitude.
أنظر إلى موقفك المرتزقة.
It's just a box of jewelry.
إنه مجرد صندوق مجوهرات.
What's there to be so happy about?
ما الذي يجعلنا سعداء جدًا؟
What do you know?
ماذا تعرف؟
If only I had met Lord Shen earlier.
لو التقيت باللورد شين في وقت سابق.
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
Rest assured.
اطمئن، لا تشغل بالك.
As long as you work hard,
طالما أنك تعمل بجد،
I will reward you accordingly.
سأكافئك وفقًا لذلك.
Then I thank you...
ثم أشكرك...
in advance.
مقدماً.
Making an empty promise again.
تقديم وعد فارغ مرة أخرى.
I came this time
لقد جئت هذه المرة
to fulfill my promise.
لتنفيذ وعدي.
The reward I promised you
المكافأة التي وعدتك بها
will certainly be given to you.
سيتم إعطاؤك بالتأكيد.
Thank you, My Lord.
شكرا لك يا سيدي.
Tell me, what was Lord Lu
أخبرني ما هو اللورد لو
thinking?
التفكير؟
Why is he so narcissistic?
لماذا هو نرجسي جدا؟
What's the use of having his portrait?
ما الفائدة من وجود صورته؟
Being handsome doesn't put food on the table.
إن كونك وسيمًا لا يعني وضع الطعام على المائدة.
I've thought of a way to turn this painting into money.
لقد فكرت في طريقة لتحويل هذه اللوحة إلى أموال.
What's that?
ما هذا؟
Let me tell you.
دعني أخبرك.
First, we'll do this.
أولاً، سنفعل هذا.
Zhao.
تشاو.
Do you think Officer Huang
هل تعتقد أن الضابط هوانغ
is still related
لا يزال مرتبطا
to the relief fund robbery case?
إلى قضية سرقة صندوق الإغاثة؟
I don't think so.
أنا لا أعتقد ذلك.
I think Officer Huang is a kind and honest person,
أعتقد أن الضابط هوانغ شخص طيب وصادق،
always willing to help others.
دائما على استعداد لمساعدة الآخرين.
Huang Yu!
هوانغ يو!
Don't rush! Don't push!
لا تستعجل! لا تدفع!
There's enough for everyone!
هناك ما يكفي للجميع!
Money for the portrait, on the spot!
المال للصورة، على الفور!
Everyone, don't push.
الجميع، لا تدفعوا.
There's enough for everyone.
هناك ما يكفي للجميع.
Don't push.
لا تدفع.
Pay first, then you get the portrait!
ادفع أولاً، ثم تحصل على الصورة!
One at a time.
واحدا تلو الآخر.
You get what you pay for.
تحصل على ما تدفعه مقابله.
Did you pay?
هل دفعت؟
There's enough for everyone!
هناك ما يكفي للجميع!
Huang Yu!
هوانغ يو!
Darn it.
لعنة عليك.
He is Lord Lu! Hurry!
إنه اللورد لو! أسرع!
Hurry.
عجل.
Lord Lu!
اللورد لو!
Don't come any closer!
لا تقترب أكثر!
Stay back!
ابقى في الخلف!
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
My Lord!
سيدي!
Huang Yu!
هوانغ يو!
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Sorry to disturb you!
آسف لإزعاجك!
Please continue.
من فضلك أستمر.
Go on.
إستمر.